Dede Badru

Software Engineer

Jl. Tegal Kawung, Kota Cimahi - 40511

dede.badrujaman@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/dedebadru

OBJECTIVE

I am a software engineer. I have worked for almost 8 years at different companies. My current position is engineer manager on WIP that owns the product ATOZPAY as an ewallet application and ATOZGO for delivery service application. My role handling the development and maintenance team especially for backend team, and coordination with other divisions.

EDUCATION

- Universitas Nurtanio Bandung Teknik Informatika
- SMK Negeri 11 Bandung Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak

RELATED EXPERIENCES

Engineer Manager, Weyland Indonesia Perkasa (2019 - Present)

Lead Software Engineer, Weyland Indonesia Perkasa (2017 - 2019)

Lead Frontend Developer, Appschef (2016 - 2017)

Lead Developer, Walden Global Services (2015 - 2016)

Developer, Walden Global Services (2013 - 2014)

RELATED SKILL

Framework Programming
Javascript
Database engine
Ruby on Rails, and Laravel
Vuejs, Angular, and Jquery
MySQL, and postgreSQL

• Subversion : Git

• Environments Dev : Vagrant, Docker

• Cloud : AWS, and Digital Ocean

• Operating system : UNIX